Your LLM application has eval coverage that goes green on every CI run.
Three weeks after launch, production hallucinates a model brownout and
your retry logic hides the failure for five seconds. pytest-resilience-agent
closes that gap.
A typical eval suite scores the clean path. It does not inject chaos at
the gateway, the MCP server, or the rate limiter. The faults that wake
you up at two in the morning live in that layer, and no scored eval
catches them.
Resilience tests live on a different axis from eval tests. The eval
suite measures what you can imagine; the resilience suite reacts to what
production actually throws. Both matter. They compose without overlap.
Step one. The plugin talks to the Lark MCP server and pulls the failing
tests in your project. Three failures arrive, each carrying its
last-failure string. The pipeline takes those strings as the input
signal.
Step two. The generator matches each failure string against a regex
rule set and picks the chaos scenarios that reproduce the failure. The
rules are deterministic. Anyone reading the project can audit the
mapping in thirty seconds.
Step three. The plugin installs the chosen scenarios via respx, an
httpx transport mock. The application under test sees a real broken
gateway, not a mocked client in its own code. Same code path as
production, controlled fault injection at the wire.
Step four. Tests pass under controlled chaos, the plugin reports each
resolution back to Lark, and the Lark failure UI now shows the new
pytest path next to the original failure. The loop closes.
The whole pipeline is one pytest plugin with one marker, two fixtures,
and a transport-layer mock. Same scenarios work against the OpenAI SDK,
Anthropic SDK, or raw httpx. End-user code does not change.
Sixteen tests pass at submission, nine chaos scenarios ship in the box,
and the full Lark to pytest to resolution loop runs in one command on a
clean checkout. No external accounts required.
pytest-resilience-agent. Open source on GitHub. Built on Lark MCP, the
TrueFoundry AI Gateway, and pytest for the DevNetwork AI plus ML
Hackathon 2026. Thanks for watching.